

# **AXEL TAVARES**

## **OBJECTIVE**

I have 5 years of experience working on retail 4 years of experience in storage business managing, and 2 year experience as a hospital Senior Patient Access Representative and a total of 10 years of customer service experience. I am a great hands-on learner and always aim for perfection. I am eager to apply my Computer knowledge and managing service skills on this position.

## **EXPERIENCE**

## SENIOR PATIENT ACCESS • UNIVERSITY OF MIAMI HOSPIAL • 2022-PRESENT

As a Senior Patient Access Representative, I have the same duties as a Patient Access Representative but deal with certain clinic duties other PARs don't. I make sure all my teammates are working together doing a good job and giving a great customer service. Being a Senior PAR means I am the leader of the team, and I must guide and help my teammates when they need assistance. I mentor them so they can grow and help them when they have questions or complications at the job. I am also the person that reports to the supervisor and keeps them informed about clinic performance or about any concerns and issues that might occur in the clinic. I also make sure I do a great job and give the best customer service to serve as an example to my teammates.

#### PATIENT ACCESS • UNIVERSITY OF MIAMI HOSPIAL • 2021-2022

Help patients with the check-in and check-out process when they are present at the hospital. I make sure the patient chart is completed so that they can proceed to their appointments. Also, help the patient to make sure they leave the hospital with their future appointments and testing scheduled during the check-out process. I am well trained on the EPIC system and use it in combination with the NICE system. I call the patients to help them schedule any future appointment or active order they might have pending for the future. So far, I have been well trained in the Cardiology, Pulmonology, Gastroenterology, Physical Therapy, and UPAC clinics and I am looking forward to learn about more clinics in the future.

#### STORE MANAGER • CUBESMART • 2017 - 2020

Responsible for 700 plus storage units, managing the office, and keeping the storage site and the office clean and in order. Call customer top set up appointments to show them the facility and what size storage fits them. Rent the cube to the customer, resolve customer issues, and manage the customers' accounts. Responding to customers complaints and emails and







## **SKILLS**

- Bilingual, (English/Spanish)
- C programming language (Basic)
- Java programming language (Basic)
- IT Tech support (Intermediate)
- Customer Service
- Computer Hardware Knowledgeable

## **CERTIFICATES**

 Google IT Professional Certificate. calling regarding any certain issues. Took customer payments and oversaw the office money deposits. Always available at the office to resolve customers issues or helping them in any way possible by phone or email.

#### STOCK SUPERVISOR • KIPLING • 2015 - 2017

Responsible for the merchandise and inventory of the store and offsite storage. Kept every piece of merchandise counted and organized by model and color. I had three people that I managed and helped me with organizing and making sure all products were in stock. Receive shipments and ensured merchandise was prepared. While at the store I became a floor manager and helped customer finding the product they needed or help with any issue or questions they might have.

## **EDUCATION**

#### **COMPUTER SCIENCE • CURRENTLY ENROLLED • FIU**

Moved back to Florida and currently enrolled in FIU pursuing a bachelor's degree in computer science.

## **COMPUTER SCIENCE • JUNE 2019 - DECEMBER 2020 • UMGC**

Moved to Maryland and changed major from Criminal Justice to Computer Science.

AA IN CRIMINAL JUSTICE • MAY 2019 • BROWARD COLLEGE

Graduated with Honors with a GPA of 3.30.

HIGH SCHOOL • JUNE 2013 • CYPRESS BAY HIGH SCHOOL High School Diploma.